<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

  <string name="app_name">Beigesoft™ EIS</string>
  <string name="share">Share files</string>
  <string name="port">Port:</string>
  <string name="start">Start</string>
  <string name="stop">Stop</string>
  <string name="starting">Starting</string>
  <string name="stopping">Stopping</string>
  <string name="ksPassw">Password:</string>
  <string name="ksPasswRep">Confirm password:</string>
  <string name="ajettyNumber">A-Jetty number:</string>
  <string name="passwNoMatch">The passwords do not match!</string>
  <string name="EnterAjettyNumber">Please enter A-Jetty number!</string>
  <string name="ajettycacopied">A-Jetty CA certificat ajetty-ca[A-Jetty#].peme and file exchanger public key ajetty-file-exch[A-Jetty#].kpub has been created.</string>
  <string name="passwordWrong">Wrong password!</string>
  <string name="enterPassw">Please enter password!</string>
  <string name="sendingStart">Sending request to start server, please wait&#8230;</string>
  <string name="cantStart">Can not start A-Jetty!</string>
  <string name="cantInitCrypto">Can not initialize crypto service!</string>
  <string name="cantCrDir">Can not create ks directory</string>
  <string name="ksDirRules">KS directory must contains only ks file!!!</string>
  <string name="wasErr">There was errors!</string>
  <string name="newFlCop">New version of WEB static files has been copied!</string>
  <string name="dirCrFlCop">Beige Accounting directory has been  successfully created and WEB static files has been copied!</string>
  <string name="srvStrt">A-Jetty has been started.</string>
  <string name="noPerm">No permissions!</string>
  <string name="privTitle">Privacy policy</string>
  <string name="agree">I accept this privacy policy</string>
  <string name="urlPrv">Privacy policy page</string>
  <string name="save">Save</string>
  <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
  <string name="privAll">Beigesoft™ EIS only stores your information in database files. Log files may also contain private information.
This application is based on the built-in private A-Jetty Web server. This private Web Server is not accessible outside of your Android device. This application requires authorization with a strong password (you create a password yourself, and the software controls its reliability). This application allows a maximum of 6 failed authorization attempts. Access will be blocked for 15 minutes in case of 6 unsuccessful login attempts. You need to periodically check the logSec.log file for authorization information.
This application uses modern encryption of data passing from the server to the browser (HTTPS connection) and exchanged files (databases and log files).
Your information (SQLite database), logStd.log, logSec.log, keystore are in a place inaccessible to other software. If you forget the password from the keystore or from entering the application, then you will lose your information. Therefore, you need to make an encrypted copy of the database using the Web interface. To do this, you need a second local Beigesoft™ EIS installed on another computer or Android device. The public encryption key from the second copy of the application is used to encrypt files, and only the second application (whose public key was used to encrypt) can decrypt the transferred files. PDF reports will be uploaded to the Downloads shared folder, so avoid installing unnecessary applications that require access to the storage. When you connect your Android device to a computer in file sharing mode, any application on the computer will have direct access to these files. You need to delete these PDF files from the shared storage after viewing them.
If you are going to transfer Log files to a third party (for example, to the programmer serving this software), then you need to delete all private information from these files.
You also need to set a screen lock, such as a PIN code.
You must accept this policy in order to work with this application.
  </string>
</resources>
